[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the first pilot to make a flight at night.", "correct_answer": "Emil Aubrun", "incorrect_answers": ["Ruth Law", "Walter Brookins", "Eugene Burton"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of character did director Martin Scorsese play in his 1976 movie Taxi Driver?", "correct_answer": "Passenger in the taxi", "incorrect_answers": ["Waiter", "Salesman", "Police officer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What song is Sam playing when Rick hides the letters of transit, in the movie classic, Casablanca?", "correct_answer": "Knock on Wood", "incorrect_answers": ["Dream a Little Dream of Me", "As Time Goes By", "Boogie-Woogie Bugle Boy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which term would best describe all the people on this list: Lincoln Steffens, Ida Tarbell, Jack Anderson, Jack Newfield, Ray Stannard Baker, Wayne Barret, Richard Behar?", "correct_answer": "Muckrakers", "incorrect_answers": ["Spoonerists", "Positivists", "Playwrights"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The city of Saint Louis, nicknamed Gateway to the West, is located in which state?", "correct_answer": "Missouri", "incorrect_answers": ["Nebraska", "Mississippi", "Ohio"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In a game of Pinochle, what is the second highest ranking card?", "correct_answer": "Ten", "incorrect_answers": ["Nine", "Ace", "King"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is a name of a Truffaut movie?", "correct_answer": "Day for Night", "incorrect_answers": ["Days of  Leaud", "Days in Calabria", "Days in Algiers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who plays the role of the narrator in the 2001 movie Carmen: A Hip Hopera?", "correct_answer": "Da Brat", "incorrect_answers": ["Joy Bryant", "Queen Latifah", "Wyclef Jean"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Barn Owl likes to sleep all day long.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What famous landmark is featured in the beginning of the movie A View to a Kill?", "correct_answer": "The Eiffel Tower in Paris", "incorrect_answers": ["The Brandenburg Gate in Berlin", "The Colosseum in Rome", "The Taj Mahal in India"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The cerebellum section of the brain controls the fine movement and equilibrium, among other things.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What rapper starred alongside Whoopi Goldberg in the 2001 dramedy movie Kingdom Come?", "correct_answer": "LL Cool J", "incorrect_answers": ["Busta Rhymes", "Will Smith", "All of these"]}]